# https://opentdb.com/api_config.php

question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The main character in the &quot;Half-Life&quot; franchise is named Morgan Freeman.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Musicals & Theatres", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the play Oedipus Rex, Oedipus kills his father due to jealousy in loving his mother.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario 64&quot;, collecting 100 coins on a level will give you a 1-UP.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Linus Torvalds created Linux and Git.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "There is a city called Rome in every continent on Earth.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A universal set, or a set that contains all sets, exists.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Science: Mathematics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "The &#039;Squaring the Circle&#039; problem is solvable.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Studio Ghibli is a Japanese animation studio responsible for the films &quot;Wolf Children&quot; and &quot;The Boy and the Beast&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Animals", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science: Computers", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Ada Lovelace is often considered the first computer programmer.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "Ottawa is the capital of Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "History", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "United States President John F. Kennedy was assassinated during his presidential motorcade in Atlanta, Georgia on November 22nd, 1963.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The PlayStation was originally a joint project between Sega and Sony that was a Sega Genesis with a disc drive.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Ewan McGregor did not know the name of the second prequel film of Star Wars during and after filming.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "question": "There are no deserts in Europe.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Vehicles", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The full English name of the car manufacturer BMW is Bavarian Motor Works", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Gosho Aoyama Made This Series: (Detective Conan \/ Case Closed!)", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Books", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "Stephen Chbosky wrote the book &#039;The Perks of Being A Wallflower&#039;.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Splatoon, the Squid Sisters are named Tako and Yaki.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In Sonic the Hedgehog universe, Tails&#039; real name is Miles Prower.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In the &quot;Toaru Kagaku no Railgun&quot; anime,  espers can only reach a maximum of level 6 in their abilities.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The name of the attack &quot;Kamehameha&quot; in Dragon Ball Z was named after a famous king of Hawaii.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Sports", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Roger Federer is a famous soccer player.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon Sun and Moon, a male Salandit can evolve to a Salazzle.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Brandon Routh plays the titular character in the movie &quot;John Wick&quot;.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In Pok&eacute;mon, Arbok evolves into Seviper.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "In Battlestar Galactica (2004), Cylons were created by man as cybernetic workers and soldiers.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Politics", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Donald Trump won the popular vote in the 2016 United States presidential election.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Star Trek&quot;, Klingons are aliens.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "An average human can go two weeks without water.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Cartoon & Animations", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Waylon Smithers from &quot;The Simpsons&quot; was originally black when he first appeared in the series.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;27 Club&quot; is a term used to refer to a list of famous actors, musicians, and artists who died at the age of 27.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Several characters in &quot;Super Mario 64&quot; blink their eyes, including Mario himself.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Sonic the Hedgehog 2&quot; originally was going to have a time travel system.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Film", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "&quot;Foodfight!&quot; earned less than $80,000 at box office.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Music", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "John Williams composed the music for &quot;Star Wars&quot;.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Television", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                       "question": "&quot;The Simpsons&quot; family is named after creator Matt Groening&#039;s real family.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There are 2 player roles in Trouble in Terrorist Town.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
                                      "question": "Doki Doki Literature Club was developed in Japan.",
                                      "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Each piece in Tetris is called a tetris.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The mitochondria is the powerhouse of the cell.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "In &quot;Space Station 13&quot;,  the station has a clown aboard it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
